neighbor.report 2019-07-30

# Privacy Policy - Neighbor.Report

Last Updated: December 6, 2017

Neighbor Report (“NR”) is the provider of the neighbor.report website and all users of neighbor.report are subject to this Privacy Policy, Terms and Conditions, Terms of Use and any additional policies NR publishes on the neighbor.report website. 

NR’s Privacy Policy explains the manner in which NR collects, shares and/or uses any and/or all user provided information on neighbor.report, including any and all personal information that users of neighbor.report provide. 

NR may at its own discretion amend or change this Privacy Policy at any time. The latest version of NR’s Privacy Policy can be found at **https://neighbor.report/privacy**. Through the continued access of neighbor.report, any users whether registered or guest, accept any changes, amendments or revisions made to this Privacy Policy. 

**ANY USERS OF THE NEIGHBOR.REPORT WEBSITE THAT DO NOT AGREE TO THIS POLICY MUST IMMEDIATELY STOP ANY AND ALL USE OF NEIGHBOR.REPORT. BY USING OR ACCESSING THE NEIGHBOR.REPORT WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY.**

## I. Available Information on the neighbor.report website:

a. NR combines information which is publicly available from sources such as but not limited to: (i) social networks/social media; (ii) phone books, (iii) voting party affiliation; (iv)market surveys; (v) real estate listings; (vi) public court records; and (vii) additional public resources (“Public Information”). NR makes this Public Information available to users and NR Account holders through, the neighbor.report website. The Public Information available on neighbor.report, is not verified by NR, nor is the Public Information guaranteed to be accurate, legitimate, legal or most recently by NR. 

b. Personal Information, that is provided by users of neighbor.report and published on neighbor.report is part of the Public Information and is available to all users of the neighbor.report website. 

c. Personal Information that is provided by users of neighbor.report at the time the users register for an account, is not part of the Public Information and will not be available to other users of neighbor.report. 

d. NR cannot remove any information from any aforementioned third-party public sources, such as social networks, social media, phone books, voting party affiliation, market surveys, real estate listings, public court records and other similar public resources. 

## II. NR’s Collection of Personal Information:

a. Users of neighbor.report, can do so without creating an account on the neighbor.report website. NR is still able to collect information from unregistered users of neighbor.report. Such information can include IP address information used in accessing the neighbor.report website and user activity on neighbor.report through the use of cookies. Cookies are minor text files which are stored on computers and/or other devices used to access neighbor.report, which store information about user visits to neighbor.report. 

b. NR collects information provided by users when creating an account on neighbor.report, including but not limited to the registered users name, email address, mailing address and/or any other information requested by NR needed for registering an account on neighbor.report. 

c. NR may preserve user search history on neighbor.report. NR may utilize users search history in order to provide updates and/or notifications relevant to the user’s previous searches on neighbor.report, help us improve the user experience and provided additional services on neighbor.report. NR does not share user search history with third parties except in cases where sharing user search history is necessary and required by law, or in the event NR has a reasonable, good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to comply with: (i) service of legal process on NR; (ii) for the protection and or defense of the rights and property of NR, its users; (iii) in order to protect someone’s safety in an emergency situation. 

d. NR may use any information that is uploaded, imported and/or downloaded on neighbor.report. 

e. Third party password manager applications for mobile and desktops, may leave credentials when logging into neighbor.report. NR may store these login credentials in accordance with strict security standards. 

## III. NR’s Sharing and Use of Personal Information:

a. NR may use Personal Information provided by users in creating their account on neighbor.report, to send e-mails pertaining to services provided by NR, such as but not limited to new services that may be forthcoming to neighbor.report. NR may employ the services of trusted third parties in order to improve, promote, protect and/or provide services that may be offered on neighbor.report. Such trusted third parties may access users Personal Information solely for the performance of tasks on behalf of NR and in full compliance with this Privacy Policy. NR is not involved in the exchange, giving, sale or transfer of user provided Personal Information for creating an account on neighbor.report to any other company except as specifically noted herein. Any Personal Information provided by NR to another company except as in the aforementioned example, will not occur without users consent. 

b. NR may use Personal Information provided by users on neighbor.report in order to make improvements to our services and offerings. Additionally, NR may share the IP address of users that was used to access neighbor.report with certain third parties for the purpose of detecting and preventing fraud. NR may also use other third party companies’ technology and services in helping NR understand in the way that neighbor.report users make use of the site. As a result, certain information about usage of neighbor.report by its users, may be accessible to the aforementioned third party companies for the purpose of improving user experience on neighbor.report. NR actively protects the anonymity of the users of neighbor.report, and does not distribute information that would be personally identifiable of its user’s activity and usage on neighbor.report, other than as described herein or in II (c). Any aforementioned shared data with third parties, is aggregated to only show use and not a user’s personally identifiable information. 

c. NR reserves its right to transfer Personal Information in the event of succession of NR’s business to any successor in interest. 

d. This Privacy Policy describes NR’s handling of personally identifiable information as deemed by the California Online Privacy Protection Act. 

## IV. Privacy of Children:

a. NR’s website, neighbor.report is intended and directed to users who are at least eighteen (18) years old. NR does not knowingly collect any Personal Information from users who are under the age of eighteen (18). Any user of neighbor.report who is aware that NR has collected Personal Information from a person under the age of eighteen (18), please immediately notify NR by filling remove form, and the Personal Information will be removed from the neighbor.report website as quickly and as reasonably possible. This provision of NR’s Privacy Policy regarding the collection of data from persons under the age of eighteen (18), meets and exceeds the requirements of the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. 

b. NR does not knowingly aggregate or provide any Public Information about persons under the age of eighteen (18). 

## V. Contact NR:

a. Questions regarding NR’s Privacy Policy may be directed to ****.
